Eric Nelson II

(510) 327-9419 nelsoneric2011@gmail.com

Objective

To gain experience within a business environment, and be able to make significant contributions that will lead to company success and career growth. Also having the opportunity to use my leadership, problem solving, communication, and team working skills that I've developed over the course of college and work experience.

Work Experience

CodeFu Instructor

September 2018-present November 2016-present

- · Teach computational Logic of Computer Science
 - o Using boardgames, robots, Scratch Jr, students will learn the basics of Computer Programing.
 - Students will gain a understanding of sprites, variables, loops, and functions by coding the own stores, games, and interactive apps.
- Promote cooperative social development by encouraging students to problem solve and debug their code together.

Freelance Graphic Designer

November 2016-present

- · Create visual concepts, by hand or using computer software, to communicate ideas that inspire, inform, or captivate consumers.
- · Using adobe suit, application most used illustrator and photoshop
- Develop the overall layout and production design for advertisements, brochures, magazines, and corporate reports.

Apple Retail

Apple Union Square, San Francisco, Ca U.S. 03/2016-07/2018

Technical Specialist

- Develop strong, positive relationships with Apple
- Maintain composure and customer focus while trouble shooting
- Explore option for customer needs
- Empathizing with customers problems
- Time management and quick decision making
- ACMT (Apple certified Mac technician)

H&M Sales Advisor

Westfield Mall, San Francisco, Ca U.S. 09/2015- 02/2016

- Cash handling
- Creative visual set-up
- Flexibility in all store functions

Conference and Events

California Baptist University, Riverside, CA U.S. 06/2014 - 08/2015

- Prepared Apartment/Dorms for companies or camps that used the school's facilities
- Events set up and break down, ie: stage set up and break down and AV installation and troubleshooting
- Basic office filing and answering phones for company clients
- Provide customer service

Education

Merritt College Oakland, CA U.S.

A.A. in Accounting, GPA: 3.0

2011 - 2013

- · General Education
- Captain of the Men's Basketball Team
- Lead team to the State Payoffs
- Won 1st All Conference and Team MVP

California Baptist University Riverside, CA U.S.

B.A. in Business Administration, GPA: 3.0

2013 - 2015

- Played on Men's Basketball Team
- Won the Conference Championship
 - Achieved NCAA Division II Regional Championship

UC Berkeley Extension program

Full Stack coding program

2018-Present

- knowledge of Networking, Database, User Interface, API, Security etc.
- Web Development for both front-end and back-end portions of an application.

Relevant Coursework

- Managerial Accounting
 Corporate Finance
 Quantitative Business Analysis
 Leadership Organization
 Communication

- Strategy in Management

- Skills/Strengths
 Proficient in Excel, PowerPoint, Microsoft Word
 - Team worker
 - Leadership skills Self-motivated

 - Communication skills
 - Problem-solving skills Html, CSS, Javascript